<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout android:gravity="fill_horizontal" android:orientation="vertical" android:id="@id/page2" android:background="#ffffffff" android:visibility="gone" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:layout_alignParentLeft="true" android:layout_centerVertical="true"
  xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">
    <LinearLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="fill_parent" android:layout_weight="1.0">
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingTop="@dimen/a10dp" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="17 U.S. Code • 117 - Limitations on exclusive rights: Computer programs" />
        <View android:background="#ffdddddd" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="@dimen/a1dp" />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(a) Making of Additional Copy or Adaptation by Owner of Copy. - Notwithstanding the provisions of section 106, it is not an infringement for the owner of a copy of a computer program to make or authorize the making of another copy or adaptation of that computer program provided:  \n (1) that such a new copy or adaptation is created as an essential step in the utilization of the computer program in conjunction with a machine and that it is used in no other manner, or  \n (2) that such new copy or adaptation is for archival purposes only and that all archival copies are destroyed in the event that continued possession of the computer program should cease to be rightful." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(b) Lease, Sale, or Other Transfer of Additional Copy or Adaptation. - Any exact copies prepared in accordance with the provisions of this section may be leased, sold, or otherwise transferred, along with the copy from which such copies were prepared, only as part of the lease, sale, or other transfer of all rights in the program. Adaptations so prepared may be transferred only with the authorization of the copyright owner." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(c) Machine Maintenance or Repair. - Notwithstanding the provisions of section 106, it is not an infringement for the owner or lessee of a machine to make or authorize the making of a copy of a computer program if such copy is made solely by virtue of the activation of a machine that lawfully contains an authorized copy of the computer program, for purposes only of maintenance or repair of that machine, if -  \n (1) such new copy is used in no other manner and is destroyed immediately after the maintenance or repair is completed; and  \n (2) with respect to any computer program or part thereof that is not necessary for that machine to be activated, such program or part thereof is not accessed or used other than to make such new copy by virtue of the activation of the machine." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(d) Definitions. - For purposes of this section -  \n (1) the &quot;maintenance&quot; of a machine is the servicing of the machine in order to make it work in accordance with its original specifications and any changes to those specifications authorized for that machine; and  \n (2) the &quot;repair&quot; of a machine is the restoring of the machine to the state of working in accordance with its original specifications and any changes to those specifications authorized for that machine." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="17 U.S. Code• 118 - Scope of exclusive rights: Use of certain works in connection with noncommercial broadcasting" />
        <View android:background="#ffdddddd" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="@dimen/a1dp" />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(a) The exclusive rights provided by section 106 shall, with respect to the works specified by subsection (b) and the activities specified by subsection (d),(!1) be subject to the conditions and limitations prescribed by this section." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(b) Notwithstanding any provision of the antitrust laws, any owners of copyright in published nondramatic musical works and published pictorial, graphic, and sculptural works and any public broadcasting entities, respectively, may negotiate and agree upon the terms and rates of royalty payments and the proportionate division of fees paid among various copyright owners, and may designate common agents to negotiate, agree to, pay, or receive payments.\n  (1) Any owner of copyright in a work specified in this subsection or any public broadcasting entity may submit to the Copyright Royalty Judges proposed licenses covering such activities with respect to such works.\n  (2) License agreements voluntarily negotiated at any time between one or more copyright owners and one or more public broadcasting entities shall be given effect in lieu of any determination by the Librarian of Congress or the Copyright Royalty Judges, if copies of such agreements are filed with the Copyright Royalty Judges within 30 days of execution in accordance with regulations that the Copyright Royalty Judges shall issue.\n  (3) Voluntary negotiation proceedings initiated pursuant to a petition filed under section 804(a) for the purpose of determining a schedule of terms and rates of royalty payments by public broadcasting entities to copyright owners in works specified by this subsection and the proportionate division of fees paid among various copyright owners shall cover the 5-year period beginning on January 1 of the second year following the year in which the petition is filed. The parties to each negotiation proceeding shall bear their own costs.\n  (4) In the absence of license agreements negotiated under paragraph (2) or (3), the Copyright Royalty Judges shall, pursuant to chapter 8, conduct a proceeding to determine and publish in the Federal Register a schedule of rates and terms which, subject to paragraph (2), shall be binding on all owners of copyright in works specified by this subsection and public broadcasting entities, regardless of whether such copyright owners have submitted proposals to the Copyright Royalty Judges. In establishing such rates and terms the Copyright Royalty Judges may consider the rates for comparable circumstances under voluntary license agreements negotiated as provided in paragraph (2) or (3). The Copyright Royalty Judges shall also establish requirements by which copyright owners may receive reasonable notice of the use of their works under this section, and under which records of such use shall be kept by public broadcasting entities." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(c) Subject to the terms of any voluntary license agreements that have been negotiated as provided by subsection (b)(2) or (3), a public broadcasting entity may, upon compliance with the provisions of this section, including the rates and terms established by the Copyright Royalty Judges under subsection (b)(4), to the extent that they were accepted by the Librarian of Congress, engage in the following activities with respect to published nondramatic musical works and published pictorial, graphic, and sculptural works:\n  (1) performance or display of a work by or in the course of a transmission made by a noncommercial educational broadcast station referred to in subsection (g); (!1) and\n  (2) production of a transmission program, reproduction of copies or phonorecords of such a transmission program, and distribution of such copies or phonorecords, where such production, reproduction, or distribution is made by a nonprofit institution or organization solely for the purpose of transmissions specified in paragraph (1); and\n  (3) the making of reproductions by a governmental body or a nonprofit institution of a transmission program simultaneously with its transmission as specified in paragraph (1), and the performance or display of the contents of such program under the conditions specified by paragraph (1) of section 110, but only if the reproductions are used for performances or displays for a period of no more than seven days from the date of the transmission specified in paragraph (1), and are destroyed before or at the end of such period. No person supplying, in accordance with paragraph (2), a reproduction of a transmission program to governmental bodies or nonprofit institutions under this paragraph shall have any liability as a result of failure of such body or institution to destroy such reproduction: Provided, That it shall have notified such body or institution of the requirement for such destruction pursuant to this paragraph: And provided further, That if such body or institution itself fails to destroy such reproduction it shall be deemed to have infringed." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(d) Except as expressly provided in this subsection, this section shall have no applicability to works other than those specified in subsection (b). Owners of copyright in nondramatic literary works and public broadcasting entities may, during the course of voluntary negotiations, agree among themselves, respectively, as to the terms and rates of royalty payments without liability under the antitrust laws. Any such terms and rates of royalty payments shall be effective upon filing with the Copyright Royalty Judges, in accordance with regulations that the Copyright Royalty Judges shall prescribe as provided in section 803(b)(6).\n\n  (e) Nothing in this section shall be construed to permit, beyond the limits of fair use as provided by section 107, the unauthorized dramatization of a nondramatic musical work, the production of a transmission program drawn to any substantial extent from a published compilation of pictorial, graphic, or sculptural works, or the unauthorized use of any portion of an audiovisual work.\n\n  (f) As used in this section, the term &quot;public broadcasting entity&quot; means a noncommercial educational broadcast station as defined in section 397 of title 47 and any nonprofit institution or organization engaged in the activities described in paragraph (2) of subsection (c)." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="18 U.S. Code• 48 - Depiction of animal cruelty" />
        <View android:background="#ffdddddd" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="@dimen/a1dp" />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(a) Creation, Sale, or Possession. - Whoever knowingly creates, sells, or possesses a depiction of animal cruelty with the intention of placing that depiction in interstate or foreign commerce for commercial gain, shall be fined under this title or imprisoned not more than 5 years, or both.\n\n  (b) Exception. - Subsection (a) does not apply to any depiction that has serious religious, political, scientific, educational, journalistic, historical, or artistic value.\n\n  (c) Definitions. - In this section - \n  (1) the term &quot;depiction of animal cruelty&quot; means any visual or auditory depiction, including any photograph, motion-picture film, video recording, electronic image, or sound recording of conduct in which a living animal is intentionally maimed, mutilated, tortured, wounded, or killed, if such conduct is illegal under Federal law or the law of the State in which the creation, sale, or possession takes place, regardless of whether the maiming, mutilation, torture, wounding, or killing took place in the State; and\n  (2) the term &quot;State&quot; means each of the several States, the District of Columbia, the Commonwealth of Puerto Rico, the Virgin Islands, Guam, American Samoa, the Commonwealth of the Northern Mariana Islands, and any other commonwealth, territory, or possession of the United States." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="18 U.S. Code• 1084 - Transmission of wagering information; penalties" />
        <View android:background="#ffdddddd" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="@dimen/a1dp" />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(a) Whoever being engaged in the business of betting or wagering knowingly uses a wire communication facility for the transmission in interstate or foreign commerce of bets or wagers or information assisting in the placing of bets or wagers on any sporting event or contest, or for the transmission of a wire communication which entitles the recipient to receive money or credit as a result of bets or wagers, or for information assisting in the placing of bets or wagers, shall be fined under this title or imprisoned not more than two years, or both.\n\n  (b) Nothing in this section shall be construed to prevent the transmission in interstate or foreign commerce of information for use in news reporting of sporting events or contests, or for the transmission of information assisting in the placing of bets or wagers on a sporting event or contest from a State or foreign country where betting on that sporting event or contest is legal into a State or foreign country in which such betting is legal.\n\n  (c) Nothing contained in this section shall create immunity from criminal prosecution under any laws of any State.\n\n  (d) When any common carrier, subject to the jurisdiction of the Federal Communications Commission, is notified in writing by a Federal, State, or local law enforcement agency, acting within its jurisdiction, that any facility furnished by it is being used or will be used for the purpose of transmitting or receiving gambling information in interstate or foreign commerce in violation of Federal, State or local law, it shall discontinue or refuse, the leasing, furnishing, or maintaining of such facility, after reasonable notice to the subscriber, but no damages, penalty or forfeiture, civil or criminal, shall be found against any common carrier for any act done in compliance with any notice received from a law enforcement agency. Nothing in this section shall be deemed to prejudice the right of any person affected thereby to secure an appropriate determination, as otherwise provided by law, in a Federal court or in a State or local tribunal or agency, that such facility should not be discontinued or removed, or should be restored.\n\n  (e) As used in this section, the term “State” means a State of the United States, the District of Columbia, the Commonwealth of Puerto Rico, or a commonwealth, territory or possession of the United States." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="18 U.S. Code• 1509 - Obstruction of court orders" />
        <View android:background="#ffdddddd" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="@dimen/a1dp" />
        <TextView android:textSize="12.0sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="Whoever, by threats or force, willfully prevents, obstructs, impedes, or interferes with, or willfully attempts to prevent, obstruct, impede, or interfere with, the due exercise of rights or the performance of duties under any order, judgment, or decree of a court of the United States, shall be fined under this title or imprisoned not more than one year, or both. No injunctive or other civil relief against the conduct made criminal by this section shall be denied on the ground that such conduct is a crime." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="18 U.S. Code• 1510 - Obstruction of criminal investigations" />
        <View android:background="#ffdddddd" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="@dimen/a1dp" />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(a) Whoever willfully endeavors by means of bribery to obstruct, delay, or prevent the communication of information relating to a violation of any criminal statute of the United States by any person to a criminal investigator shall be fined under this title, or imprisoned not more than five years, or both.\n\n  (b)\n  (1) Whoever, being an officer of a financial institution, with the intent to obstruct a judicial proceeding, directly or indirectly notifies any other person about the existence or contents of a subpoena for records of that financial institution, or information that has been furnished in response to that subpoena, shall be fined under this title or imprisoned not more than 5 years, or both.\n\n  (2) Whoever, being an officer of a financial institution, directly or indirectly notifies—\n  (A) a customer of that financial institution whose records are sought by a subpoena for records; or\n  (B) any other person named in that subpoena;\n  about the existence or contents of that subpoena or information that has been furnished in response to that subpoena, shall be fined under this title or imprisoned not more than one year, or both.\n  (3) As used in this subsection—\n  (A) the term “an officer of a financial institution” means an officer, director, partner, employee, agent, or attorney of or for a financial institution; and\n  (B) the term “subpoena for records” means a Federal grand jury subpoena or a Department of Justice subpoena (issued under section 3486 of title 18), for customer records that has been served relating to a violation of, or a conspiracy to violate—\n  (i) section 215, 656, 657, 1005, 1006, 1007, 1014, 1344, 1956, 1957, orchapter 53 of title 31; or\n  (ii) section 1341 or 1343 affecting a financial institution.\n\n  (c) As used in this section, the term “criminal investigator” means any individual duly authorized by a department, agency, or armed force of the United States to conduct or engage in investigations of or prosecutions for violations of the criminal laws of the United States.\n\n  (d)\n  (1) Whoever—\n  (A) acting as, or being, an officer, director, agent or employee of a person engaged in the business of insurance whose activities affect interstate commerce, or\n  (B) is engaged in the business of insurance whose activities affect interstate commerce or is involved (other than as an insured or beneficiary under a policy of insurance) in a transaction relating to the conduct of affairs of such a business,\n  with intent to obstruct a judicial proceeding, directly or indirectly notifies any other person about the existence or contents of a subpoena for records of that person engaged in such business or information that has been furnished to a Federal grand jury in response to that subpoena, shall be fined as provided by this title or imprisoned not more than 5 years, or both.\n  (2) As used in paragraph (1), the term “subpoena for records” means a Federal grand jury subpoena for records that has been served relating to a violation of, or a conspiracy to violate, section 1033 of this title.\n  (e) Whoever, having been notified of the applicable disclosure prohibitions or confidentiality requirements of section 2709 (c)(1) of this title, section 626(d)(1) or 627(c)(1) of the Fair Credit Reporting Act (15 U.S.C. 1681u (d)(1) or 1681v (c)(1)),section 1114(a)(3)(A) or 1114(a)(5)(D)(i) of the Right to Financial Privacy Act [1] (12 U.S.C. 3414 (a)(3)(A) or 3414 (a)(5)(D)(i)), orsection 802(b)(1) of the National Security Act of 1947 (50 U.S.C. 436 (b)(1)), [2] knowingly and with the intent to obstruct an investigation or judicial proceeding violates such prohibitions or requirements applicable by law to such person shall be imprisoned for not more than five years, fined under this title, or both." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="18 U.S. Code• 1801 - Video voyeurisms" />
        <View android:background="#ffdddddd" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="@dimen/a1dp" />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(a) Whoever, in the special maritime and territorial jurisdiction of the United States, has the intent to capture an image of a private area of an individual without their consent, and knowingly does so under circumstances in which the individual has a reasonable expectation of privacy, shall be fined under this title or imprisoned not more than one year, or both.\n\n  (b) In this section -\n  (1) the term &quot;capture&quot;, with respect to an image, means to videotape, photograph, film, record by any means, or broadcast;\n  (2) the term &quot;broadcast&quot; means to electronically transmit a visual image with the intent that it be viewed by a person or persons;\n  (3) the term &quot;a private area of the individual&quot; means the naked or undergarment clad genitals, pubic area, buttocks, or female breast of that individual;\n  (4) the term &quot;female breast&quot; means any portion of the female breast below the top of the areola; and\n  (5) the term &quot;under circumstances in which that individual has a reasonable expectation of privacy&quot; means -\n  (A) circumstances in which a reasonable person would believe that he or she could disrobe in privacy, without being concerned that an image of a private area of the individual was being captured; or\n  (B) circumstances in which a reasonable person would believe that a private area of the individual would not be visible to the public, regardless of whether that person is in a public or private place.\n\n  (c) This section does not prohibit any lawful law enforcement, correctional, or intelligence activity." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="18 U.S. Code• 2252 - Certain activities relating to material involving the sexual exploitation of minors" />
        <View android:background="#ffdddddd" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="@dimen/a1dp" />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(a) Any person who -\n  (1) knowingly transports or ships in interstate or foreign commerce by any means including by computer or mails, any visual depiction, if -\n  (A) the producing of such visual depiction involves the use of a minor engaging in sexually explicit conduct; and\n  (B) such visual depiction is of such conduct;\n  (2) knowingly receives, or distributes, any visual depiction that has been mailed, or has been shipped or transported in interstate or foreign commerce, or which contains materials which have been mailed or so shipped or transported, by any means including by computer, or knowingly reproduces any visual depiction for distribution in interstate or foreign commerce or through the mails, if -\n  (A) the producing of such visual depiction involves the use of a minor engaging in sexually explicit conduct; and\n  (B) such visual depiction is of such conduct;\n  (3) either -\n  (A) in the special maritime and territorial jurisdiction of the United States, or on any land or building owned by, leased to, or otherwise used by or under the control of the Government of the United States, or in the Indian country as defined in section 1151 of this title, knowingly sells or possesses with intent to sell any visual depiction; or\n  (B) knowingly sells or possesses with intent to sell any visual depiction that has been mailed, or has been shipped or transported in interstate or foreign commerce, or which was produced using materials which have been mailed or so shipped or transported, by any means, including by computer, if -\n  (i) the producing of such visual depiction involves the use of a minor engaging in sexually explicit conduct; and\n  (ii) such visual depiction is of such conduct; or\n  (4) either -\n  (A) in the special maritime and territorial jurisdiction of the United States, or on any land or building owned by, leased to, or otherwise used by or under the control of the Government of the United States, or in the Indian country as defined in section 1151 of this title, knowingly possesses 1 or more books, magazines, periodicals, films, video tapes, or other matter which contain any visual depiction; or\n  (B) knowingly possesses 1 or more books, magazines, periodicals, films, video tapes, or other matter which contain any visual depiction that has been mailed, or has been shipped or transported in interstate or foreign commerce, or which was produced using materials which have been mailed or so shipped or transported, by any means including by computer, if -\n  (i) the producing of such visual depiction involves the use of a minor engaging in sexually explicit conduct; and\n  (ii) such visual depiction is of such conduct; shall be punished as provided in subsection (b) of this section.\n\n  (b)(1) Whoever violates, or attempts or conspires to violate, paragraphs (!1) (1), (2), or (3) of subsection (a) shall be fined under this title and imprisoned not less than 5 years and not more than 20 years, but if such person has a prior conviction under this chapter, chapter 71, chapter 109A, or chapter 117, or under section 920 of title 10 (article 120 of the Uniform Code of Military Justice), or under the laws of any State relating to aggravated sexual abuse, sexual abuse, or abusive sexual conduct involving a minor or ward, or the production, possession, receipt, mailing, sale, distribution, shipment, or transportation of child pornography, such person shall be fined under this title and imprisoned for not less than 15 years nor more than 40 years.\n  (2) Whoever violates, or attempts or conspires to violate, paragraph (4) of subsection (a) shall be fined under this title or imprisoned not more than 10 years, or both, but if such person has a prior conviction under this chapter, chapter 71, chapter 109A, or chapter 117, or under section 920 of title 10 (article 120 of the Uniform Code of Military Justice), or under the laws of any State relating to aggravated sexual abuse, sexual abuse, or abusive sexual conduct involving a minor or ward, or the production, possession, receipt, mailing, sale, distribution, shipment, or transportation of child pornography, such person shall be fined under this title and imprisoned for not less than 10 years nor more than 20 years.\n\n  (c) Affirmative Defense. - It shall be an affirmative defense to a charge of violating paragraph (4) of subsection (a) that the defendant -\n  (1) possessed less than three matters containing any visual depiction proscribed by that paragraph; and\n  (2) promptly and in good faith, and without retaining or allowing any person, other than a law enforcement agency, to access any visual depiction or copy thereof -\n  (A) took reasonable steps to destroy each such visual depiction; or\n  (B) reported the matter to a law enforcement agency and afforded that agency access to each such visual depiction." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="18 U.S. Code• 2252A - Certain activities relating to material constituting or containing child pornography" />
        <View android:background="#ffdddddd" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="@dimen/a1dp" />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(a) Any person who -\n  (1) knowingly mails, or transports or ships in interstate or foreign commerce by any means, including by computer, any child pornography;\n  (2) knowingly receives or distributes - \n  (A) any child pornography that has been mailed, or shipped or transported in interstate or foreign commerce by any means, including by computer; or\n  (B) any material that contains child pornography that has been mailed, or shipped or transported in interstate or foreign commerce by any means, including by computer;\n  (3) knowingly -\n  (A) reproduces any child pornography for distribution through the mails, or in interstate or foreign commerce by any means, including by computer; or\n  (B) advertises, promotes, presents, distributes, or solicits through the mails, or in interstate or foreign commerce by any means, including by computer, any material or purported material in a manner that reflects the belief, or that is intended to cause another to believe, that the material or purported material is, or contains -\n  (i) an obscene visual depiction of a minor engaging in sexually explicit conduct; or\n  (ii) a visual depiction of an actual minor engaging in sexually explicit conduct;\n  (4) either -\n  (A) in the special maritime and territorial jurisdiction of the United States, or on any land or building owned by, leased to, or otherwise used by or under the control of the United States Government, or in the Indian country (as defined in section 1151), knowingly sells or possesses with the intent to sell any child pornography; or\n  (B) knowingly sells or possesses with the intent to sell any child pornography that has been mailed, or shipped or transported in interstate or foreign commerce by any means, including by computer, or that was produced using materials that have been mailed, or shipped or transported in interstate or foreign commerce by any means, including by computer;\n  (5) either -\n  (A) in the special maritime and territorial jurisdiction of the United States, or on any land or building owned by, leased to, or otherwise used by or under the control of the United States Government, or in the Indian country (as defined in section 1151), knowingly possesses any book, magazine, periodical, film, videotape, computer disk, or any other material that contains an image of child pornography; or\n  (B) knowingly possesses any book, magazine, periodical, film, videotape, computer disk, or any other material that contains an image of child pornography that has been mailed, or shipped or transported in interstate or foreign commerce by any means, including by computer, or that was produced using materials that have been mailed, or shipped or transported in interstate or foreign commerce by any means, including by computer; or\n  (6) knowingly distributes, offers, sends, or provides to a minor any visual depiction, including any photograph, film, video, picture, or computer generated image or picture, whether made or produced by electronic, mechanical, or other means, where such visual depiction is, or appears to be, of a minor engaging in sexually explicit conduct -\n  (A) that has been mailed, shipped, or transported in interstate or foreign commerce by any means, including by computer;\n  (B) that was produced using materials that have been mailed, shipped, or transported in interstate or foreign commerce by any means, including by computer; or\n  (C) which distribution, offer, sending, or provision is accomplished using the mails or by transmitting or causing to be transmitted any wire communication in interstate or foreign commerce, including by computer, for purposes of inducing or persuading a minor to participate in any activity that is illegal.(!1) shall be punished as provided in subsection (b).\n\n  (b)(1) Whoever violates, or attempts or conspires to violate, paragraph (1), (2), (3), (4), or (6) of subsection (a) shall be fined under this title and imprisoned not less than 5 years and not more than 20 years, but, if such person has a prior conviction under this chapter, chapter 71, chapter 109A, or chapter 117, or under section 920 of title 10 (article 120 of the Uniform Code of Military Justice), or under the laws of any State relating to aggravated sexual abuse, sexual abuse, or abusive sexual conduct involving a minor or ward, or the production, possession, receipt, mailing, sale, distribution, shipment, or transportation of child pornography, such person shall be fined under this title and imprisoned for not less than 15 years nor more than 40 years.\n  (2) Whoever violates, or attempts or conspires to violate, subsection (a)(5) shall be fined under this title or imprisoned not more than 10 years, or both, but, if such person has a prior conviction under this chapter, chapter 71, chapter 109A, or chapter 117, or under section 920 of title 10 (article 120 of the Uniform Code of Military Justice), or under the laws of any State relating to aggravated sexual abuse, sexual abuse, or abusive sexual conduct involving a minor or ward, or the production, possession, receipt, mailing, sale, distribution, shipment, or transportation of child pornography, such person shall be fined under this title and imprisoned for not less than 10 years nor more than 20 years.\n\n  (c) It shall be an affirmative defense to a charge of violating paragraph (1), (2), (3)(A), (4), or (5) of subsection (a) that -\n  (1)(A) the alleged child pornography was produced using an actual person or persons engaging in sexually explicit conduct; and\n  (B) each such person was an adult at the time the material was produced; or\n  (2) the alleged child pornography was not produced using any actual minor or minors. No affirmative defense under subsection (c)(2) shall be available in any prosecution that involves child pornography as described in section 2256(8)(C). A defendant may not assert an affirmative defense to a charge of violating paragraph (1), (2), (3)(A), (4), or (5) of subsection (a) unless, within the time provided for filing pretrial motions or at such time prior to trial as the judge may direct, but in no event later than 10 days before the commencement of the trial, the defendant provides the court and the United States with notice of the intent to assert such defense and the substance of any expert or other specialized testimony or evidence upon which the defendant intends to rely. If the defendant fails to comply with this subsection, the court shall, absent a finding of extraordinary circumstances that prevented timely compliance, prohibit the defendant from asserting such defense to a charge of violating paragraph (1), (2), (3)(A), (4), or (5) of subsection (a) or presenting any evidence for which the defendant has failed to provide proper and timely notice.\n\n  (d) Affirmative Defense. - It shall be an affirmative defense to a charge of violating subsection (a)(5) that the defendant -\n  (1) possessed less than three images of child pornography; and\n  (2) promptly and in good faith, and without retaining or allowing any person, other than a law enforcement agency, to access any image or copy thereof -\n  (A) took reasonable steps to destroy each such image; or\n  (B) reported the matter to a law enforcement agency and afforded that agency access to each such image.\n  (e) Admissibility of Evidence. - On motion of the government, in any prosecution under this chapter or section 1466A, except for good cause shown, the name, address, social security number, or other nonphysical identifying information, other than the age or approximate age, of any minor who is depicted in any child pornography shall not be admissible and may be redacted from any otherwise admissible evidence, and the jury shall be instructed, upon request of the United States, that it can draw no inference from the absence of such evidence in deciding whether the child pornography depicts an actual minor.\n  (f) Civil Remedies. -\n  (1) In general. - Any person aggrieved by reason of the conduct prohibited under subsection (a) or (b) or section 1466A may commence a civil action for the relief set forth in paragraph (2).\n  (2) Relief. - In any action commenced in accordance with paragraph (1), the court may award appropriate relief, including -\n  (A) temporary, preliminary, or permanent injunctive relief;\n  (B) compensatory and punitive damages; and\n  (C) the costs of the civil action and reasonable fees for attorneys and expert witnesses." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="18 U.S. Code• 2252B - Misleading domain names on the Internet" />
        <View android:background="#ffdddddd" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="@dimen/a1dp" />
        <TextView android:textSize="12.0sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(a) Whoever knowingly uses a misleading domain name on the Internet with the intent to deceive a person into viewing material constituting obscenity shall be fined under this title or imprisoned not more than 2 years, or both.\n\n  (b) Whoever knowingly uses a misleading domain name on the Internet with the intent to deceive a minor into viewing material that is harmful to minors on the Internet shall be fined under this title or imprisoned not more than 4 years, or both.\n\n  (c) For the purposes of this section, a domain name that includes a word or words to indicate the sexual content of the site, such as &quot;sex&quot; or &quot;porn&quot;, is not misleading.\n  (d) For the purposes of this section, the term &quot;material that is harmful to minors&quot; means any communication, consisting of nudity, sex, or excretion, that, taken as a whole and with reference to its context -\n  (1) predominantly appeals to a prurient interest of minors;\n  (2) is patently offensive to prevailing standards in the adult community as a whole with respect to what is suitable material for minors; and\n  (3) lacks serious literary, artistic, political, or scientific value for minors.\n  (e) For the purposes of subsection (d), the term &quot;sex&quot; means acts of masturbation, sexual intercourse, or physcial (!1) contact with a person's genitals, or the condition of human male or female genitals when in a state of sexual stimulation or arousal." />
        <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/a12sp" android:textStyle="bold" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="18 U.S. Code• 2257 - Record keeping requirements" />
        <View android:background="#ffdddddd" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="@dimen/a1dp" />
        <TextView android:textSize="12.0sp" android:textColor="#ff000000" android:gravity="left" android:paddingBottom="@dimen/a8dp" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:text="(a) Whoever produces any book, magazine, periodical, film, videotape, digital image, digitally- or computer-manipulated image of an actual human being, picture, or other matter which—\n  (1) contains one or more visual depictions made after November 1, 1990 of actual sexually explicit conduct; and\n  (2) is produced in whole or in part with materials which have been mailed or shipped in interstate or foreign commerce, or is shipped or transported or is intended for shipment or transportation in interstate or foreign commerce;\n  shall create and maintain individually identifiable records pertaining to every performer portrayed in such a visual depiction.\n\n  (b) Any person to whom subsection (a) applies shall, with respect to every performer portrayed in a visual depiction of actual sexually explicit conduct—\n  (1) ascertain, by examination of an identification document containing such information, the performer’s name and date of birth, and require the performer to provide such other indicia of his or her identity as may be prescribed by regulations;\n  (2) ascertain any name, other than the performer’s present and correct name, ever used by the performer including maiden name, alias, nickname, stage, or professional name; and\n  (3) record in the records required by subsection (a) the information required by paragraphs (1) and (2) of this subsection and such other identifying information as may be prescribed by regulation.\n\n  (c) Any person to whom subsection (a) applies shall maintain the records required by this section at his business premises, or at such other place as the Attorney General may by regulation prescribe and shall make such records available to the Attorney General for inspection at all reasonable times.\n\n  (d)\n  (1) No information or evidence obtained from records required to be created or maintained by this section shall, except as provided in this section, directly or indirectly, be used as evidence against any person with respect to any violation of law.\n  (2) Paragraph (1) of this subsection shall not preclude the use of such information or evidence in a prosecution or other action for a violation of this chapter or chapter 71, or for a violation of any applicable provision of law with respect to the furnishing of false information.\n\n  (e)\n  (1) Any person to whom subsection (a) applies shall cause to be affixed to every copy of any matter described in paragraph (1) of subsection (a) of this section, in such manner and in such form as the Attorney General shall by regulations prescribe, a statement describing where the records required by this section with respect to all performers depicted in that copy of the matter may be located. In this paragraph, the term “copy” includes every page of a website on which matter described in subsection (a) appears.\n  (2) If the person to whom subsection (a) of this section applies is an organization the statement required by this subsection shall include the name, title, and business address of the individual employed by such organization responsible for maintaining the records required by this section.\n\n  (f) It shall be unlawful—\n  (1) for any person to whom subsection (a) applies to fail to create or maintain the records as required by subsections (a) and (c) or by any regulation promulgated under this section;\n  (2) for any person to whom subsection (a) applies knowingly to make any false entry in or knowingly to fail to make an appropriate entry in, any record required by subsection (b) of this section or any regulation promulgated under this section;\n  (3) for any person to whom subsection (a) applies knowingly to fail to comply with the provisions of subsection (e) or any regulation promulgated pursuant to that subsection;\n  (4) for any person knowingly to sell or otherwise transfer, or offer for sale or transfer, any book, magazine, periodical, film, video, or other matter, produce in whole or in part with materials which have been mailed or shipped in interstate or foreign commerce or which is intended for shipment in interstate or foreign commerce, which—\n  (A) contains one or more visual depictions made after the effective date of this subsection of actual sexually explicit conduct; and\n  (B) is produced in whole or in part with materials which have been mailed or shipped in interstate or foreign commerce, or is shipped or transported or is intended for shipment or transportation in interstate or foreign commerce;\n  which does not have affixed thereto, in a manner prescribed as set forth in subsection (e)(1), a statement describing where the records required by this section may be located, but such person shall have no duty to determine the accuracy of the contents of the statement or the records required to be kept; and\n  (5) for any person to whom subsection (a) applies to refuse to permit the Attorney General or his or her designee to conduct an inspection under subsection (c).\n\n  (g) The Attorney General shall issue appropriate regulations to carry out this section.\n\n  (h) In this section—\n  (1) the term “actual sexually explicit conduct” means actual but not simulated conduct as defined in clauses (i) through (v) of section 2256 (2)(A) of this title;\n  (2) the term “produces”—\n  (A) means—\n  (i) actually filming, videotaping, photographing, creating a picture, digital image, or digitally- or computer-manipulated image of an actual human being;\n  (ii) digitizing an image, of a visual depiction of sexually explicit conduct; or, assembling, manufacturing, publishing, duplicating, reproducing, or reissuing a book, magazine, periodical, film, videotape, digital image, or picture, or other matter intended for commercial distribution, that contains a visual depiction of sexually explicit conduct; or\n  (iii) inserting on a computer site or service a digital image of, or otherwise managing the sexually explicit content, [1] of a computer site or service that contains a visual depiction of, sexually explicit conduct; and\n  (B) does not include activities that are limited to—\n  (i) photo or film processing, including digitization of previously existing visual depictions, as part of a commercial enterprise, with no other commercial interest in the sexually explicit material, printing, and video duplication;\n  (ii) distribution;\n  (iii) any activity, other than those activities identified in subparagraph (A), that does not involve the hiring, contracting for, managing, or otherwise arranging for the participation of the depicted performers;\n  (iv) the provision of a telecommunications service, or of an Internet access service or Internet information location tool (as those terms are defined in section 231 of the Communications Act of 1934 (47 U.S.C. 231)); or\n  (v) the transmission, storage, retrieval, hosting, formatting, or translation (or any combination thereof) of a communication, without selection or alteration of the content of the communication, except that deletion of a particular communication or material made by another person in a manner consistent with section 230(c) of the Communications Act of 1934 (47 U.S.C. 230 (c)) shall not constitute such selection or alteration of the content of the communication; and\n  (3) the term “performer” includes any person portrayed in a visual depiction engaging in, or assisting another person to engage in, sexually explicit conduct.\n\n  (i) Whoever violates this section shall be imprisoned for not more than 5 years, and fined in accordance with the provisions of this title, or both. Whoever violates this section after having been convicted of a violation punishable under this section shall be imprisoned for any period of years not more than 10 years but not less than 2 years, and fined in accordance with the provisions of this title, or both." />
    </LinearLayout>
</LinearLayout>